Guide to the Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Hospital Administration, 1948-1960; Series IV
  - 1945-1951
    - Student Material - thru 1951 (Box 451, Folder 396-398)
  - 1945-1960
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1950 (Box 452, Folder 399-400)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1951 (Box 452, Folder 401-402)
    - George Buis et al; Correspondence and other material - misc. 1951 (Box 453, Folder 403-406)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1951 (Box 454, Folder 407)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1952 (Box 454, Folder 408-409)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1955 (Box 454, Folder 410-411)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1956 (Box 454, Folder 412)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1945-1951 (Worcester Hospital) (Box 455, Folder 413)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1945-1951 (Belmont Hospital Survey) (Box 455, Folder 414)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material- misc. 1953-1955 (Box 455, Folder 415)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1956-1957 (Box 455, Folder 416)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1958 (Box 455, Folder 417-419)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1958 (Box 456, Folder 420)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1959 (Box 456, Folder 421-422)
    - George Buis et al: Correspondence and other material - misc. 1960 (Box 456, Folder 423)
    - G.N.H.H.- V.A. study (Box 456, Folder 424)
    - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation (Box 456, Folder 425)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other materials - misc. 1952 (Box 457, Folder 426-429)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1953 (Box 458, Folder 430-434)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1953 (Box 459, Folder 435)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - mist.1954 (Box 459, Folder 436)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1955 (Box 459, Folder 437)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1956 (Box 459, Folder 438-440)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1956 (Box 460, Folder 441)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1957 (Box 460, Folder 442-443)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1958 (Box 460, Folder 444)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1958 (Box 461, Folder 445)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1959 (Box 461, Folder 446-448)
    - George Buis et al: correspondence and other material - misc. 1960-1961 (Box 461, Folder 449)
    - A.H.A. - patients chart forms (Box 461, Folder 450)
    - American Medical Association (Box 461, Folder 451)
    - Army Instruction (Box 462, Folder 452)
    - Junior League Children's Hospital, Tulsa, Oklahoma (Box 462, Folder 453-454)
    - Accreditation kit (Box 462, Folder 455-456)
    - Association of University Programs in Hospital Administration - Mackinac Conference (Box 463, Folder 457)
    - Association of University Programs in Hospital Administration- Atlanta Tyler, Simmons, Sayer (Box 463, Folder 458)
    - Association of University Programs in Hospital Administration - Chicago (Box 463, Folder 459)
    - Association of University Programs in Hospital Administration Committee on Research (Box 463, Folder 460)
    - Intergovernmental relations (Box 463, Folder 461)
    - A.H.A., A.C.H.A., A.U.P.H.A. Yale alumni, Atlantic City Sept 30, Oct 1, 2, 3 (Box 463, Folder 462)
    - Cornell University A.U.P.H.A. (Box 463, Folder 463)
    - Association of University Programs in Hospital Administration (Box 464, Folder 464-465)
    - To be acknowledged (Box 464, Folder 466)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 464, Folder 467-469)
    - Health Insurance Council (Box 465, Folder 470)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association (Box 465, Folder 471)
    - Conn. Hospital Association Diet and Personnel Project Final Report, S. Knox, G.S.B. (Box 465, Folder 472)
    - Frank M. Coffin (Box 465, Folder 473)
    - Hospital Survey & Construction Program (Box 465, Folder 474)
    - American Hospital Association Hospital Schedules of Information South County Hospital (Box 465, Folder 475-476)
    - Burroughs Accounting Equipment and Techniques for Hospitals (Box 465, Folder 477)
    - White House Conference (Doris Haas - chairman) (Box 465, Folder 478-479)
    - Patterns and programs of medical care (Box 466, Folder 480)
    - American College of Hospital Administrators Institute information (Box 466, Folder 481)
    - Grace-New Haven Hospital Fee schedule. Dec 1, 1948 (Box 466, Folder 482)
    - American College of Hospital Administrators First Preceptor Training Program (Box 466, Folder 483)
    - Hospital Administration Miscellaneous information (Box 466, Folder 484)
    - George Buis (Box 466, Folder 485)
    - University Education in Hospital Administration (Commission on) (Box 466, Folder 486)
    - University Education Hospital Commission, Olsen (Box 466, Folder 487)
    - American Hospital Association Hospital Schedules of Information (Box 466, Folder 488)
    - American College of Hospital Administrators Preceptor Conference (Box 466, Folder 489)
    - American College of Hospital Administrators Preceptor Conference Group Reports (Box 467, Folder 490)
    - Grace-New Haven Community Hospital International Hospital Federation Study Tour (Box 467, Folder 491)
    - Summary of a Conference of University Programs in Hospital Administration 1950, The Graduate Record Examinations (Box 467, Folder 492)
    - New London Survey (Box 467, Folder 493)
    - Public Health in Hartford 1955 (Box 467, Folder 494)
    - Derby Report I (Box 467, Folder 495)
    - Derby Report II (Box 467, Folder 496)
    - Holden Hospital (Box 467, Folder 497)
    - Surveys - General (Box 468, Folder 498)
    - Yale Department of Public Health Miscellaneous materials (Box 468, Folder 499-501)
    - Department of Public Health Miscellaneous documents and reports (Box 468, Folder 503)
    - New England Hospital Assembly (Box 468, Folder 504)
    - George Buis - personnel (Box 468, Folder 505)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1945-1950 (Box 468, Folder 506)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1950-1955 (Box 469, Folder 507)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1957-1959 (Box 469, Folder 508)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1960-1961 (Box 469, Folder 509-510)
    - Miscellaneous materials Teaching outlines, etc. (Box 469, Folder 511-512)
    - Miscellaneous minutes, 1960 (Box 469, Folder 513)
    - Miscellaneous minutes, 1960 (Box 470, Folder 514)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1960 (Box 470, Folder 515-517)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, 1960 (Box 470, Folder 518-519)
    - Miscellaneous reports, 1959-1960 (Box 470, Folder 520)
    - Miscellaneous reports, 1959-1960 (Box 471, Folder 521-522)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1959-1960 (Box 471, Folder 523-525)
    - The Accreditation of North American Schools of Public Health (Box 471, Folder 526-527)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1959-1960 (Box 472, Folder 528)
    - First Class Mail received & acknowledged (Box 472, Folder 529)
    - Second Class Mail (Box 472, Folder 530)
    - Photostated copies (Box 472, Folder 531)
- Finances and Grants, 1952-1960; Series V
  - U S P H S CS 545 C5 Cancer control, 1952-1955 (Box 473, Folder 1)
  - U S P H S CS 9218, 1953-1955 (Box 473, Folder 2)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 National Heart Institute, 1955-1956 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 Expense accounts, 1955 (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 Miscellaneous charges, 1955 (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 Request for check, 1955 (Box 473, Folder 6)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 University charges, 1955 (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C6 Mental Health, 1954-1955 (Box 473, Folder 8)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C6 Expense accounts, 1955 (Box 473, Folder 9)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C6 Transfers, 1955 (Box 473, Folder 10)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C6 University stock charges, 1955 (Box 473, Folder 11)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C7 Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 473, Folder 12)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C7 Expense accounts, 1955-1956 (Box 473, Folder 13)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C7 Financial statements, 1956-1957 (Box 473, Folder 14)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C7 Transfers, 1955-1957 (Box 473, Folder 15)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C7 University stock charges, 1956 (Box 473, Folder 16)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 473, Folder 17)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C Expense accounts, 1955-1956 (Box 473, Folder 18)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C Financial statements, 1955-1956 (Box 473, Folder 19)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C Miscellaneous charges, 1955-1956 (Box 473, Folder 20)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C Transfers, 1956-1957 (Box 473, Folder 21)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C University stock charges, 1956 (Box 473, Folder 22)
  - U S P H S W-53 Hospital Facilities: correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 473, Folder 23)
  - U S P H S W-53 Hospital Facilities Financial statements, 1955-1957 (Box 473, Folder 24)
  - U S P H S W-53 Hospital Facilities Miscellaneous charges, 1956-1957 (Box 473, Folder 25)
  - U S P H S W-53 Hospital Facilities Expense accounts, 1956-1957 (Box 473, Folder 26)
  - U S P H S W-53 Hospital Facilities Transfers, 1957 (Box 473, Folder 27)
  - U S P H S W-53 Hospital Facilities University stock charges, 1957 (Box 473, Folder 28)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C2 Heart: correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 473, Folder 29)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C2 Heart: expense accounts, 1956-1957 (Box 473, Folder 30)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C2 Heart: financial statement, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 31)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C2 Heart: miscellaneous charges, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 32)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C2 Heart: transfers, 1957 (Box 474, Folder 33)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C2 Heart: university stock charges, 1957 (Box 474, Folder 34)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 Statistical: correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 35)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 Statistical: expense accounts, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 36)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 Statistical: financial statements, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 37)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 Statistical: miscellaneous charges, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 38)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 Statistical: transfers, 1957 (Box 474, Folder 39)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 Statistical: university stock charges, 1957 (Box 474, Folder 40)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C8 Mental Health: correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 474, Folder 41)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C8 Mental Health: expense accounts, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 42)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C8 Mental Health: financial statements, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 43)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C8 Mental Health: miscellaneous charges, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 44)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C8 Mental Health: university stock charges, 1957 (Box 474, Folder 45)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 Psychiatric Hospital Administration correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 474, Folder 46)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 474, Folder 47)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: expense accounts, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 48)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: financial statements, 1955-1957 (Box 474, Folder 49)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: miscellaneous charges, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 50)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: university stock charges, 1956-1957 (Box 474, Folder 51)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 Application, 1957 (Box 474, Folder 52)
  - U S P H S W-53 C Hospital Facilities: correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 474, Folder 53)
  - U S P H S W-53 C Hospital Facilities: expense reports, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 54)
  - U S P H S W-53 C Hospital Facilities: financial statements, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 55)
  - U S P H S W-53 C Hospital Facilities: miscellaneous charges, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 56)
  - U S P H S W-53 C Hospital Facilities: transfers, 1958-1959 (Box 475, Folder 57)
  - U S P H S W-53 C Hospital Facilities: university stock charges, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 58)
  - U S P H S W-53 C Hospital Facilities: request for check, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 59)
  - U S P H S W-53 C Hospital Facilities: telephone, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 60)
  - U S P H S HT 5083 C3 Heart: correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 475, Folder 61)
  - U S P H S HT 5083 C3 Heart: expense accounts, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 62)
  - U S P H S HT 5083 C3 Heart: financial statement, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 63)
  - U S P H S HT 5083 C3 Heart: miscellaneous charges, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 64)
  - U S P H S HT 5083 C3 Heart: request for check, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 65)
  - U S P H S HT 5083 C3 Heart: transfers, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 66)
  - U S P H S HT 5083 C3 Heart: university stock charges, 1958 (Box 475, Folder 67)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 C (2G 47) Statistical: correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 68)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 C (2G 47) Statistical: expense accounts, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 69)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 C Statistical: financial statements, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 70)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 C Statistical: transfers, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 71)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 C Statistical: miscellaneous charges, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 72)
  - U S P H S HTS 5119 C Statistical: university stock charges, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 73)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C9 Mental Health: correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 475, Folder 74)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C9 Mental Health: expense accounts, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 75)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C9 Mental Health: financial statements, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 76)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C9 Mental Health: miscellaneous charges, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 77)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C9 Mental Health: transfers, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 78)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C9 Mental Health: university stock charges, 1957-1958 (Box 475, Folder 79)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C1 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 80)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C1 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: financial statements, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 81)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C1 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: expense accounts, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 82)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C1 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: miscellaneous charges, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 83)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C1 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: transfers, 1957 (Box 476, Folder 84)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C1 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: university stock charges, 1958 (Box 476, Folder 85)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 (2G-5) Epidemiology: correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 86)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 Epidemiology: correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 87)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 Epidemiology: expense accounts, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 88)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 Epidemiology: financial statements, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 89)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 Epidemiology: miscellaneous charges, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 90)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 Epidemiology: request for check, 1958 (Box 476, Folder 91)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 Epidemiology: transfers, 1958 (Box 476, Folder 92)
  - U S P H S 2M 6586 Epidemiology: university stock charges, 1957-1958 (Box 476, Folder 93)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C4 Heart: correspondence, 1958 (Box 476, Folder 94)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C4 Heart: training grant, 1 September 1958-1931 August 1960 (Box 476, Folder 95)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C4 Heart: expense accounts, 1959 (Box 476, Folder 96)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C4 Heart: financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 476, Folder 97)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C4 Heart: miscellaneous charges, 1959 (Box 476, Folder 98)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C4 Heart: request for check, 1959 (Box 476, Folder 99)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C4 Heart: transfers, 1958-1959 (Box 476, Folder 100)
  - U S P H S HT 5085 C4 Heart: university stock charges, 1959 (Box 476, Folder 101)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C10 Mental Health: correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 476, Folder 102)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C10 Mental Health: expense accounts, 1958-1959 (Box 476, Folder 103)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C10 Mental Health: financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 104)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C10 Mental Health: transfers, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 105)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C10 Mental Health: miscellaneous charges, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 106)
  - U S P H S 2M 5277 C10 Mental Health: university stock charges, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 107)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 (C1) C2 Psychiatric Hospital Administration, 1957-1959 (Box 477, Folder 108)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C2 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 477, Folder 109)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C2 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: expense accounts, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 110)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C2 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 111)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C2 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: miscellaneous charges, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 112)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C2 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: transfers, 1958 (Box 477, Folder 113)
  - U S P H S 2M 6253 C2 Psychiatric Hospital Administration: University stock charges, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 114)
  - U S P H S 2G-5 C1 Epidemiology: Graduate Training Grant, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 115)
  - U S P H S 2G-5 C1 Epidemiology: correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 116)
  - U S P H S 2G-5 C1 Epidemiology: expense accounts, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 117)
  - U S P H S 2G-5 C1 Epidemiology: financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 118)
  - U S P H S 2G-5 C1 Epidemiology: miscellaneous charges, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 119)
  - U S P H S 2G-5 C1 Epidemiology: request for check, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 120)
  - U S P H S 2G-5 C1 Epidemiology: transfers, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 121)
  - U S P H S 2G-5 C1 Epidemiology: University stock charges, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 122)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: research grant, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 123)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 477, Folder 124)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 125)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: miscellaneous charges, 1958-1959 (Box 477, Folder 126)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: request for check, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 127)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: telephone, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 128)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: transfers, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 129)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: travel expense reports, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 130)
  - U S P H S W53 C2 Hospital Facilities: University stock charges, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 131)
  - U S P H S 2G-47 C2 Statistical: correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 132)
  - U S P H S 2G-47 C2 Statistical: expense accounts, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 133)
  - U S P H S 2G-47 C2 Statistical: financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 134)
  - U S P H S 2G-47 C2 Statistical: miscellaneous charges, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 135)
  - U S P H S 2G-47 C2 Statistical: transfers, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 136)
  - U S P H S 2G-47 C2 Statistical: University stock charges, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 137)
  - U S P H S CS-9073 C9 Occupational Medicine, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 138)
  - U S P H S Title I 59-105 Yale Traineeships: correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 139)
  - U S P H S Title I 59-105 Yale Traineeships: financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 140)
  - U S P H S Title I 59-105 Yale Traineeships: Georges, Ferne Marie, M.D., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 141)
  - U S P H S Title I 59-105 Yale Traineeships: Richards, Lois Key, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 142)
  - U S P H S Title I 59-105 Yale Traineeships: Tufts, Norman R., D.V.M., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 143)
  - U S P H S Title I 59-105 Yale Traineeships: Schlesinger, Richard H., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 144)
  - U S P H S Title I 59-105 Yale Traineeships: Washburn, Frederick C., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 145)
  - U S P H S Title I Washington Traineeships: correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 146)
  - U S P H S Title I Washington Traineeships: Carmichael, Thomas, 1958 (Box 478, Folder 147)
  - U S P H S Title I Washington Traineeship: Coniglio, Constance A., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 148)
  - U S P H S Title I Washington Traineeships: Enowitch, Bennett I., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 149)
  - U S P H S Title I Washington Traineeship: Lavenhar, Marvin A., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 151)
  - U S P H S Title I Washington Traineeships: Plumb, Carl S., M.D., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 152)
  - U S P H S Title I Washington Traineeships: Orgain, H. Harold, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 153)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse NT-43C) correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 154)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse NT-43C) financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 155)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse) Dingman, Rita, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 156)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse) Hofer, Folly, 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 157)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse) Koehler, Ericka J., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 158)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse) Remillet, June W. (Mrs.), 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 159)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse) Thomson, Janet L., 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 160)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse) Wade, Mattie Lee (Mrs.), 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 161)
  - U S P H S Title II Yale Traineeships (Nurse) Wilson, Dorothy M. (Mrs.), 1958-1959 (Box 478, Folder 162)
  - Terminated Mental Health Grants: 2M 5277 C2, C3, C4, C5, 1949-1954 (Box 479, Folder 163)
  - Pending and Rejected Grants: G-3370, 2M-5781, G-3648 P.H. 1, RG-2498, -2307, -2257, -2885, 1949-1951 (Box 479, Folder 164)
  - Expired Grants: RG-1754 (R), -1072,(C) -1072, -1487 (C), 1771-A, MHT C-328 1A, 1949-1951 (Box 479, Folder 165)
  - Expired Grants - Departmental: USPHS 3-M-9057, CS 9218, 1957 (Box 479, Folder 166)
  - Cancer Grants: CS-545 (C, C2, C3, C4), C-545, 1948-1957 (Box 480, Folder 168)
  - Current Grants - Departmental: Psychiatric Hospital Administration, HT-5085, USPHS CS-545 (C5), Institute of Occupational Medicine, USPHS C5, 1954-1956 (Box 480, Folder 169)
  - Expense Accounts - Agency Survey, 1958-1959 (Box 480, Folder 170)
  - Expense Accounts, I. V. Hiscock - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 171)
  - Financial Statement - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 172)
  - Honoraria - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 173)
  - Miscellaneous Charges - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 174)
  - Miscellaneous Charges - Dr. Herbert R. Edwards, Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 175)
  - Request for Check - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 176)
  - Transfers - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 177)
  - Telephone and Telegraph, I.V. Hiscock - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 178)
  - Deposits - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 179)
  - Deposits, regular - Agency Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 180)
  - Financial Statement E 50-25-17, 1956-1957 (Box 480, Folder 181)
  - Honoraria and Expense Accounts E 50-25-17, 1954-1955 (Box 480, Folder 182)
  - Honoraria and Expense Accounts E 50-25-17, 1955-1956 (Box 481, Folder 183)
  - Financial Statement E 50-25-17 (02-41-50-25-17), 1957-1958 (Box 481, Folder 184)